const quizData = [
    {
      question: "Which princess has a pet tiger named Rajah?",
      options: ["Ariel", "Jasmine", "Belle", "Aurora"],
      answer: "Jasmine"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Disney Princess lives under the sea?",
      options: ["Elsa", "Moana", "Ariel", "Rapunzel"],
      answer: "Ariel"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is known for her long magical hair?",
      options: ["Cinderella", "Mulan", "Pocahontas", "Rapunzel"],
      answer: "Rapunzel"
    },
    {
      question: "Which princess falls into a deep sleep after pricking her finger?",
      options: ["Snow White", "Aurora", "Tiana", "Merida"],
      answer: "Aurora"
    },
    {
      question: "Who dreams of opening her own restaurant?",
      options: ["Tiana", "Belle", "Cinderella", "Mulan"],
      answer: "Tiana"
    },
    {
      question: "Which princess has three fairy godmothers?",
      options: ["Ariel", "Aurora", "Moana", "Merida"],
      answer: "Aurora"
    },
    {
      question: "Which princess disguises herself as a man to join the army?",
      options: ["Merida", "Mulan", "Pocahontas", "Jasmine"],
      answer: "Mulan"
    },
    {
      question: "Which princess befriends seven dwarfs?",
      options: ["Cinderella", "Snow White", "Elsa", "Moana"],
      answer: "Snow White"
    },
    {
      question: "Who has a magical ice power?",
      options: ["Elsa", "Anna", "Rapunzel", "Merida"],
      answer: "Elsa"
    },
    {
      question: "Which princess sails across the ocean to save her people?",
      options: ["Moana", "Pocahontas", "Mulan", "Aurora"],
      answer: "Moana"
    }
  ];
  
  export default quizData;
  